Ms. Lin, you're awake?
小林老师你醒了
Did you sleep well?
睡得香吗
I fell asleep?
睡着了
Where are they?
他们人呢
They went to buy some food.
他们去买吃的了
You guys have already finished cleaning?
你们已经打扫完了
Almost.
差不多了
Ms. Lin,
小林老师
aren't you curious
你就不好奇
how you
你为什么从那个地方
ended up here?
到这里了吗
Right.
对哦
Wasn't I sleeping there?
我不在那睡的吗
That's because Coach made us do it.
那是因为教练逼我们
Be careful.
慢一点
Keep your voice down.
你小声点
Coach even reminded us
教练还提醒我们
to be quiet,
让我们小声点
afraid of waking you up.
怕吵醒你
Ms. Lin,
小林老师
you're blushing.
你脸红嘞
Am I?
红吗
It must be the heat.
热得吧
You're underestimating me if you think I'd blush over this.
因为这脸红你也太小瞧我了
-The laziest teacher in the world -They're back.
世界上最懒惰的老师
has finally woken up.
可算是睡醒了啊
I'm sorry.
不好意思啊
I got up too early this morning
起太早了
and couldn't help you out.
都没帮上你们的忙
-Boss. -It's fine. We're here, so don't worry.
老大没事 有我们放心吧
You went to buy food?
去买饭啦
How about this?
这样吧
To thank you,
为了报答你们
I'll arrange the projector myself.
我就来亲自安排下投影仪
You put in the effort, and I'll pay.
你们出力我出钱
Thank you, Ms. Lin.
谢谢小林老师
Spicy beef rice.
香辣牛肉饭
I added a steamed egg for you.
给你加了个水蒸蛋
Is there...
有没有
Yes, extra spicy,
有 多加辣椒
no cilantro.
不加香菜
-I'll take one. -Give me one.
让我挑挑 给我一张
Go away.
一边去
-Eat whatever you get. -You're not allowed to pick.
拿到啥吃啥 不给你挑
These are all...
这可都是
Thank you.
谢谢
I'm so touched.
太感动了吧
Why is there one pair of chopsticks missing?
这怎么少了一双筷子
[Receive Money by QR Code]
最后一个没筷子啊
Take his quickly!
快抢
Wait. The chopsticks are here.
别急筷子在这
I don't have my phone with me.
没带手机
Your beef is mine now.
你的牛肉归我了
Then pay me next time.
那就下次
-Lin Lu, how dare you! -The QR Code is still him.
林鹿 你胆子肥了啊
Sorry.
不好意思
Excuse me.
打扰一下
Ms. Lin, Mr. Wang,
林小姐 王先生
I brought your photos.
给你们送相片来了
These are photos of the older Lins.
这个是林老夫妇的照片
-I printed an extra set. -Thank you.
我加洗了一套
Thank you, sir.
谢谢老板
No problem.
没事
And these are your couple photos.
还有你们的情侣照片
I printed an extra set of those too.
我也加洗了一套
What... What photos?
啥 啥照片
Here.
这里啊
When I was a kid,
我小时候就在这
I attended this tutoring class.
上过这个辅导班的
At that time,
那个时候
Mr. Lin and Mr. Shen
林老师跟沈老师
provided free after-school tutoring
都是课后免费
for us students.
帮我们这帮学生做课后辅导的
So many students?
这么多学生啊
Ms. Lin, are you a teacher now?
林小姐您是不是当老师了
Yes.
是的
I also teach at Hongjing.
我也在宏景教书
That's great.
真好
I won't bother you anymore.
那我不打扰你们了
I'm leaving now.
我先走了
Goodbye.
再见啊
Thank you.
谢谢
By the way.
对了
If you two get married,
如果两位要是结婚的话
you must come to me for your wedding photos.
一定要来我这拍结婚照
I'll give you a huge discount.
我给你们打骨折
You must come.
一定要来哦
Goodbye.
再见
Getting married?
结婚啊
You guys are moving so fast?
你们进展这么快
Too fast.
太快了吧
Yes, we are having the wedding banquet next month.
对呀 下个月就要办酒了
Have you prepared the red envelopes?
你们红包准备了吗
Couple's photos?
情侣照
Let me see. Let me see.
我瞧瞧 我瞧瞧
You are a perfect match.
好配啊
Let me take a look.
让我看看
They really are couple's photos.
真是情侣照
-I knew you two would end up together. -Coach Wang.
我就知道你们俩肯定
-Aren't you going to discipline your students? -They look good together.
你的学生你不管管吗
Of course I am.
管啊
I think we should hang them on the wall
我觉得得挂在墙上
as a souvenir.
留作纪念
-Good idea.
好主意 好主意
-This is so sweet. -Are you serious?
这太甜了这个
You're afraid now?
不敢
-Then we count as the bride's family. -I've done a fortune reading, and today is a lucky day for romance.
那我们算娘家人
Hang them up then. I'm not afraid.
挂就挂 谁怕谁
-We have to back Ms. Lin up. -Yeah.
咱们得给小林老师撑腰
Kids.
孩子们
-Ms. Lin. -Coach.
小林老师 教练
The words on the blackboard are a bit faded,
这黑板上的字有点脱落了
so we touched them up.
我们给补上了
And drew some pictures.
而且还画了一些图
-Nice. -Ms. Lin.
真不错 小林老师
The rooftop is cleaned up.
天台打扫好了
You guys are so sensible,
太懂事了吧
babies.
宝宝们
No wonder I suddenly wanted to buy some fried chicken.
我想我怎么突然想去买炸鸡了
Thank you, Ms. Lin!
谢谢小林老师
-Coach, here. -Here's also iced black tea?
教练 来 这还有冰红茶
Iced black tea?
冰红茶
Iced black tea with fried chicken really hits the spot.
冰红茶配炸鸡才得劲呢
Let's go in and eat.
进去吃吧
Thank you, Ms. Lin and Coach.
谢谢小林老师教练
-You're welcome. -Ms. Lin.
不用谢 小林老师
What did you buy?
买啥了
Fried chicken. Fried chicken.
炸鸡 炸鸡
Is this the newest model that just arrived?
这是刚到的最新款吗
You must have spent a fortune.
你肯定下血本了
-Thank you, Ms. Lin.
谢谢小林老师 谢谢小林老师
You're welcome.
不用谢了
It's to reward you for your hard work.
为了犒劳一下你们的辛勤劳动
Just save me a pair of chicken wings.
给我留一对鸡翅就行了
-No problem.
没问题
-Move it over there. -Okay.
抬过去 好
-No problem.
没问题 小事
Fu, come help me.
老付 来帮我一下
-Be careful. -It's okay. Easy.
慢点慢点 没事慢点
Have some too.
你也吃啊
Here's the remote and the cable.
这是遥控器跟线
Okay.
好
-Take it over there. -Okay.
拿过去 来 好
-From today on, -Come on.
从今天起 快快快
our Yuanyuan Tutoring Class
属于我们的元元辅导班
is officially open right here.
就在这正式开张了
Okay.
好的
Nice ball.
漂亮
What a cool Marseille turn.
好帅的马赛回旋
What does that mean?
什么意思啊
It's a 180-degree spin
就是通过一百八十度旋转
to shake off the defender.
来摆脱防守者
It's Zidane's signature move.
齐达内的招牌动作
It's nothing.
这个还行吧
I once saw a youth player in England
我之前看到一个英国青训球员
who did the Marseille turn even better than this.
那马赛回旋做得比这个还溜
I know who you're talking about.
我知道你说的是哪个
He played like a genius.
他踢球就像个天才一样
He had a great season,
有个赛季踢得特别好
but there's been no news about him lately.
但现在没有信了
I don't even know if he still plays.
也不知道还踢不踢球了
Is he of Chinese descent?
是不是一个华裔
Jason.
杰森
I think so.
好像是啊
I remember he played for Nanton.
他好像是南顿的吧
Coach, you should know him, right?
教练 你应该认识吧
Look at this one!
你看这球
There's hope! There's hope!
这有希望 有希望
What a pity.
可惜
He didn't control the ball well.
没没没拿好这球
Nothing he could do. That defender is too strong.
没办法这后卫太壮了啊
There was no way to make a solo run.
怎么单刀
He lost his advantage as soon as he was blocked.
一卡就失位了
Look at their defender.
看人家这后卫
What a pity.
可惜可惜
I would've scored that.
这种球我上就好了
Wang Fa.
王法
What's wrong?
怎么了
Was that person they just mentioned
他们刚才说的
a former student of yours?
是你以前的学生
Yes.
是
Are you okay?
你还好吗
I'm fine.
还好啊
How about
要不然
we sneak out for a beer?
咱们偷偷溜出去喝啤酒
Don't drink alone.
别自己喝
Do you know the best way to drink beer?
你知道啤酒怎么样喝最好喝吗
Wait a minute.
等我一分钟
Hold this.
拿着
Watch and learn.
跟我学啊
Dig a little hole in the middle first.
先在中间挖一口心
Then dig a few times beside it.
旁边再挖两口
Scoop up
然后把旁边这些
all the little pieces scattered around.
零零散散的也挖起来
Then scoop out the pieces around the edges too.
再把边缘这些也挖起来
Use the spoon to stir it all up.
再用这个勺子搅搅搅
And now comes the main step—
然后重头戏来了
put the spoon into the bottle.
把勺子放在酒瓶里
Voilà, handmade smashed fruit beer.
纯手工手捣果啤
Try it.
尝尝
Good, right?
好喝吧
Not bad.
不错
Feeling better?
开心点了吧
Are you willing to tell me
你愿意跟我说说
about your student?
你那个学生的事吗
Why do you want to know?
你为什么想知道
In my experience,
据我的经验所谈
talking about bad things
有不好的事情把它说出来
is a good start.
就会是好的开始
A great coach from a top international club like you
你一个国际顶尖俱乐部的大教练
resigned
辞职了之后
and came to a small place like Hongjing.
来到宏景这种小地方
It's because of him, isn't it?
原因就是因为他吧
It's fine.
没事
You don't have to talk about it if you don't want to.
不愿意说也没关系
For a long time,
很长一段时间以来
I believed
我都认为
he was the most talented kid
他是我执教生涯里
I've ever met in my coaching career.
遇到过最有天赋的孩子
If that hadn't happened,
如果没有发生那件事情的话
he would be the brightest star
他现在应该是球场上
on the court right now.
最闪耀的球星
Coach.
教练
Here.
来
Thanks, Coach.
谢谢教练
There's no need to push yourself so hard.
没必要这么拼吧
You were practicing until midnight yesterday.
昨天还练习到半夜呢
The game is coming up.
快比赛了
I was just practicing my feel for the ball.
练练球感
If you can't steal it within a minute,
一分钟之内抢不到的话
go back and rest.
乖乖回去休息
Come on!
来啊
Is that all you got?
就这点水平
During that time,
那段时间
I could see that he wasn't in good shape.
我看到了他状态不好
He was always up and down.
总是起起伏伏的
I knew he was proud
我知道他骄傲
and afraid of losing.
怕输
But I didn't expect him to push himself to that extent.
但没想到他把自己逼到那个地步
Hi, Mr. Win.
你好 赢教练
Our next game is an away game.
下一场是客场
The schedule is set.
行程已经定了
We'll set off the day after tomorrow.
后天出发
Okay.
好
What did you just put away?
你刚放的什么呀
It looked like a medicine bottle.
我看是个药瓶
It's nothing.
没有
Jason.
杰森
Let me see it.
给我看看
Did he...
那他
take banned substances?
是服用了违禁药品
A routine urine test before the game
在比赛前的例行尿检
found a large amount of ephedrine in his urine.
查出他尿液里有大量的麻黄碱
For a professional player,
对一个职业球员来说
the consequences could range from suspension
轻则禁赛罚款
and fines to imprisonment.
重则判处监禁
After that incident,
那件事情之后
he was expelled from Nanton.
他就被南顿除名了
He never played football again after that.
后来他就再也没有踢过球了
What a pity.
太可惜了
Sometimes,
有的时候
if you take one wrong step,
走错一步路
there's no turning back.
就没办法再回头了
Mango or peach?
芒果味还是桃子味
Peach, of course.
当然是桃子啦
Are you feeling better?
心情好一点了吗
After all,
毕竟
it's no use being stuck in the past.
陷在过去也没有用
What you do in the future is more important, isn't it?
未来怎么做才更重要 不是吗
Hello, Ms. Lin, Coach.
小林老师 教练好
-Hello, Coach, Ms. Lin.
教练 小林老师好
-Hello. -Hello, Coach.
好 教练好
Assemble!
集合
Coming.
来了
Coach.
教练
What kind of training is it
就摆这么多标志桶
with so many cones?
是做什么训练
Physical training.
体能训练
It's very simple.
很简单
Dribble and sprint for 30 meters,
带球三十米冲刺
dribble around the cones,
带球绕桶训练
jump training,
跳跃训练
dribble around the poles,
带球绕杆
and shoot.
最后射门
That's all.
就这些
Come back!
回来
Good shot!
好球
Nice, Feng Suo.
漂亮啊 冯锁
With your physical fitness,
就凭你们这体能
I'm afraid you won't even make it to the semifinals.
恐怕连半决赛的门都摸不到
Coach,
教练
why don't you give it a try?
不行你试试
I'm hungry, bro.
我饿了 兄弟
I'm so dizzy.
好晕啊
I've lost all feeling.
没知觉了都
What is Coach going to do?
教练这是要干嘛
Why is he warming up?
他怎么开始热身了
Watch me do it.
看我做一遍
What's he doing?
干什么呀
Is he really going to try?
不会真要试吧
So cool.
太帅了
Who can keep up with this? The gap is too big.
这谁跟的上啊 差距太大了
So fast.
好快
So cool.
太帅了吧
Good ball!
好球 好球
What is Coach trying to do?
教练要整啥呀
This is too difficult.
这也太难了吧
So fast.
这么快
Such stamina and efficiency?
这体力 这效率
He even turned around?
还转身
The gap between us and him is too big.
差距也太大了吧
This is...
这是
How long did he take?
多少
Well...
这 这
That was too fast.
太快了吧
This speed.
这速度
-This speed. -Gosh.
这速度 天呐
Male animals release hormones
雄性动物散发荷尔蒙
that can easily attract females.
气场容易触达异性
It's just the natural law of attraction between males and females.
两性吸引力法则而已
Calm down.
冷静
Come here
你们过来
and look at the data.
看看刚刚的数据吧
This data is much worse than before.
这个数据比以前差太多了
I guess he's going to say this.
我猜教练肯定要说这个
We have to let the data speak.
我们要用数据说话
What you have to do next
接下来你们要做的事情
seems simple,
看似简单
but it's actually very difficult.
实则很难
Find your own data,
找到自己的数据
remember it,
记住它们
and forget everyone else's.
然后忘掉其他人的
Look at this.
你看看
Remember,
记住了
physical fitness is always the foundation.
体能永远是最基本的一项
No matter how good our tactics are
无论我们有多高超的战术
or how strong our skills are,
多么精湛的球艺
the gap in physical fitness can't be made up for.
体能的差距那就是无法弥补的
Every second you keep going on the field
你们在场上多坚持的每一秒钟
comes from the effort you put in during training.
那都是你们私底下积累的结果
Later, I'll create a physical improvement plan
之后我会给你们每个人
for each of you
根据今天的体测结果
based on today's fitness test results.
设定一个体能提升计划表
We have customized plans now.
我们也有定制的计划了
Let's train!
练
Thank you, Coach.
谢谢教练
-We must train! -I'm getting excited.
必须要练 来劲了
-Come on! -Let's go!
来吧 走
Everyone,
同学们
remember to come to Yuanyuan Tutoring Class
晚饭后记得来
for self-study after dinner!
元元辅导班上自习哦
Okay!
好的
Let's go train!
走 练
Go.
去吧
Go train!
练球去
Let's go!
走
What are we having for dinner?
晚上吃啥
That's exactly what I was thinking.
肯定我就这么想的
Did you print out the photos?
照片洗没洗啊
Let's hang up the photos, brothers.
兄弟们挂照片
[Yuanyuan Tutoring Class]
这柜子就是给我准备的啊
Me too.
我也是啊
I was looking forward to hanging the photos the most today.
我今天最期待就挂这个
They are very cool.
很帅的
I picked them for you.
给你们挑的
Yeah.
对啊
Not bad.
可以可以可以
This...
你这
Not bad, not bad.
可以 可以 可以
Let me tell you,
我告诉你
this photo must be hung right in the middle.
这张照片必须得挂在最中间
This definitely goes in the middle.
那这肯定得挂中间
Alright, I'll hang mine below.
行我挂下面吧
Don't fight over this second locker with me.
这第二个格不许跟我抢啊
Who's fighting with you?
谁跟你抢啊
You go ahead.
你来你来
We've taken a lot of photos recently.
咱们最近拍了不少照片
Let's hang them all.
都挂上
Let's just put the ball here.
球就放这吧
The photos should all be with Zheng Ren.
照片应该都在郑仁那
-I'll take the locker above yours. -You brought them, right?
那我占你上面啊
Of course I did.
那肯定的
Pick whatever you like.
随便挑
Look at these solo shots.
你们看这单张的
This one.
这个
When was this taken?
这都是啥时候拍的
You need glasses.
你该配眼镜了啊
This is the team's secret base.
这就是球队的秘密基地
What do you think? Not bad, right?
怎么样 不错吧
If you weren't next to me
要是没有你在旁边
talking non-stop,
一直说个不停
it would be much more interesting.
应该会更有趣
Why are you so mean?
你这人嘴怎么就这么欠呢
I just realized that...
我就发现
-Ms. Lin.
小林老师 小林老师
Today is Yuanyuan Tutoring Class's
今天呢 是咱们元元辅导班的
first class.
第一节课
Let's take turns giving an opening remark.
大家轮流来说一下开班寄语吧
Yuanyuan Tutoring Class, a one-of-a-kind class.
元元辅导班非常不一般
I wish everyone success in both grades and football skills.
祝大家成绩球技双丰收
I hope we can rank in the top 500
考进五百名
and keep playing football.
足球继续踢
Improve our grades
提高成绩继续踢球
With Ms. Lin teaching,
小林来授课
passing the monthly exam is a sure thing.
月考准能过
Not bad, this one.
这行啊这这这
-Not bad. -Qin Ao, your turn.
可以 秦敖秦敖你来
I...
我 我
Excuse me,
不好意思啊
Coach Wang.
王教练
You didn't answer my calls.
给您打电话您没有接
Mr. Yu Bo told me to come here to find you.
余波先生让我到这里来找您
What do you think?
您觉得怎么样
Don't be in a hurry to reject me.
您先别急着拒绝我
We are very sincere.
我们很有诚意的
Look, I came all this way.
您看我这千里迢迢地赶过来
At least give me a chance.
您至少给我一个机会吧
Let's sit down and chat.
咱们坐下来聊一聊
Then let's sit for a while.
那去坐会吧
Thank you.
谢谢
After you.
请
This stupid poacher is stealing our coach.
臭挖角的撬教练
No, I disagree.
不行我不同意啊
Come on.
不是
Will he really steal our coach?
他不会要把我们的教练给挖了吧
No! No!
不行 不行
I don't agree with it!
我不同意
What should we do then?
那咋整
Coach Wang, I've booked a table.
王教练 我订好位了
This looks so fancy.
这看起来好高级
Will they let us in dressed like this?
我们穿成这样不会不让我们进吧
I've got you covered.
有我在呢
King crab.
帝王蟹
Looking for me?
在找我吗
We're here for dinner.
我们来吃饭
What a coincidence.
好巧
Let's eat together then.
那一起吃吧
Sure.
好呀
King crab!
帝王蟹啊
Enjoy.
请慢用
Listen to the coach.
听教练的
Eat up.
快吃啊
I'll get straight to the point.
我就开门见山了
We sincerely invite you, Coach Wang,
我们诚挚地邀请王教练
to coach our team.
来指导我们球队
As far as I know,
据我所知
you haven't signed a formal contract yet.
你们还没有正式签约
Come on.
不是
Coach has already promised us.
教练都已经答应我们了
Don't waste your breath.
你就别白费力气了
Since there's no contract,
既然没有签约
there's still room for negotiation.
那一切就还有余地
Instead of wasting time
与其浪费时间
staying in a team like Hongjing,
留在宏景这样的队伍里
you should consider our team.
还不如考虑一下我们的球队
Whether it's professionalism,
不论是专业度
popularity, player quality,
知名度 球员素养
or field conditions,
又或者说场地条件
our team is a better fit for you.
我们球队更适合王教练
What kind of team is he with
什么球队啊
that he's talking so arrogantly?
说话这么狂
Mr. Wang Fa agreed
王法先生之所以会同意
to coach at Hongjing No. 8 High School
在宏景八中执教
because he saw the kids' potential.
就是看中了孩子们的潜力
Your words "wasting time"
浪费时间这四个字
have offended my students.
冒犯到我的学生了
Please take them back.
请你收回
I'm sorry.
不好意思啊
I was too eager to recruit a talent
是我求才心切
and used inappropriate words.
用词不当了
What I mean is,
我的意思是
our team
我们球队
is more suitable for Coach Wang.
更适合王教练
What's your opinion?
您的看法呢
I need to think about it.
我得考虑一下
Of course.
当然
You're Ms. Lin, right?
林老师是吗
May I ask
方便问一下
the price you offered Coach Wang?
你对王教练的开价吗
I won't beat around the bush.
我就不卖关子了
My superiors said
上面说了
that as long as Mr. Wang Fa is willing to join our team,
只要王法先生愿意来我们球队
price is not an issue.
价格不是问题
We can pay more.
我们可以加钱
I'm sorry.
不好意思啊
You won't be able
我给的价格
to outbid the offer I made.
你加不起
Coach Wang,
王教练
feel free to contact me anytime once you've made up your mind.
您考虑清楚之后随时联系我
Ms. Lin,
小林老师
you were so cool just now.
你刚才也太帅了
Your rich boss speech
你的金主发言
will be the stuff of my dreams tonight.
就是我今晚的做梦素材
Stop dreaming.
别做梦了
You're about to lose your coach.
你快没教练了
Alright.
好了
I'll go for a run first.
我就先去跑步了
Rich boss, remember to pay the bill.
金主大人记得买单
Will Coach...
教练
consider joining their team?
会考虑加入他们的队伍吗
Why would he consider
为啥考虑去
going to them?
去他那啊
Are they that awesome?
他有那么牛啊
Could it be Yongchuan Hengjiu?
难不成是永川恒久
Is Yongchuan Hengjiu...
永川恒久
really that amazing?
真那么厉害吗
All first place?
都是第一
That's really impressive.
真的很厉害
Our team is more suitable for Coach Wang.
我们球队更适合王教练
What's your opinion?
您的看法呢
I need to think about it.
我得考虑一下
Why do I have a feeling
为什么有种
that he'll break his promise?
他会背信弃义的感觉呢
What about those boys?
那帮小子怎么办
It's about time.
时间差不多了呀
Why isn't he here yet?
怎么还不见人
Is it really that hard to fake a coincidence?
假装巧遇难度这么大的吗
Ms. Lin, waiting for a sausage again?
小林老师又在等烤肠啊
Another coincidence.
还是那么巧
I'm not having sausages today.
今天不吃烤肠了
I'm opening blind boxes here.
在这拆盲盒
Here, Coach Wang, give it a try.
来 王教练也试试
You dressed like this for a night run?
你夜跑穿成这样
As long as you are determined
只要有心
to keep fit,
强身健体
does it matter what you wear?
穿成什么样重要吗
Not really.
不重要
I've gained weight lately.
我最近也胖了
I want to go for night runs with you.
我也想跟着你一起去夜跑
This isn't your usual slacker style.
这不像你咸鱼的作风
Can't a slacker move around a bit
咸鱼就不能蹦跶蹦跶
and keep fit with you?
一起强身健体啊
You unboxed the Orange!
你拆到小橙哎
I have a secret base that can cure a bad mood.
我有个秘密基地专治心情不好
Do you want to come with me?
你愿意陪我一起去吗
Thank you.
谢谢你
Let's go.
走吧
It's closed.
关门了
Hello, little babies.
哈喽 小宝宝们
Hello, Potato.
哈喽土豆
Long time no see.
好久不见啊
I'll make you cry with my kisses next time.
下回来亲哭你们
What?
什么
I mean Potato.
我是说土豆
It's the dog closest to me.
它是跟我最好的狗狗
Isn't it cute?
是不是很可爱
And that one is called Ton.
还有那只叫一吨
It was very thin when it was young,
小的时候它长得很瘦
so its mother wanted it to gain some weight.
它妈妈希望它能长得胖一点
And that one
还有那只
curled up on the sofa
窝在沙发里的狗狗
seems to have autism.
它好像有自闭症
It's called President.
叫总裁
Isn't it aloof?
是不是很高冷
These puppies
这些小狗啊
are so healing.
都特别治愈
Seeing them puts me in a good mood.
看到它们就会心情好
Wang Fa,
王法
tell me the truth.
你说实话
Are you really going to leave?
你是不是真的会走
What do you think?
你觉得呢
I think...
我觉得
Judging from your behavior,
以你的种种表现来看
you just treat yourself as a passerby.
你只是把自己当成一个过客
You are right.
你说的没错
I'm just a passerby.
我就是个过客
Then I'm doomed.
那完了
If you really leave,
你要是真走了
those naughty kids, with no one to keep them under control,
那帮熊孩子没人管
will turn this place upside down.
更是要闹上天了
Ms. Lin,
小林老师
you sound like you are accusing
你好像在指控
a wife who abandons her children
一个丈夫离婚以后
after her husband divorces her.
不管孩子的妻子
Wang Fa, I'm being serious.
王法 我在跟你说正经的
If necessary,
如果有必要的话
I can introduce you to
我可以给你介绍
some other football coaches I know.
我认识的其他一些足球教练
Coach Wang,
王教练
if I say...
如果我说
You...
你
Can you...
你可
Nothing.
没什么
Even the dogs didn't cheer me up today.
今天连看狗狗都失败了
It's getting late.
时间不早了
Go back and rest early.
早点回去休息吧
I'm hungry.
我也饿了
Time for a late-night snack.
该去吃宵夜了
Go home early then.
那早点回家
Don't be too late.
别太晚
You guys...
你们
don't go!
别走啊
Why couldn't I say something like that
怎么面对他
when I was facing him?
这种话就说不出来了呢
Zheng Feiyang, speed up!
郑飞扬速度
Gather around!
集合了
Did you skip meals?
是都没吃饭吗
You all look so listless.
一个个无精打采的
If you don't want to train, you don't have to.
如果不想训练的话可以不训练
Dismissed!
解散
Sorry.
抱歉
Sorry, Coach.
抱歉教练
We got distracted.
是我们分心了
Coach,
教练
it's not that we didn't eat.
不是我们没吃饭
We actually have a problem.
而是有问题
Speak.
说
Do you want to go to Yongchuan Hengjiu?
你是不是想去永川恒久
If so,
你要是想去
just give it to us straight, okay?
你给我们个痛快行吗
Matches
比赛
won't stop because of anyone leaving.
它不会因为任何人的离开而停止
We don't accept ambiguous answers.
模棱两可的答案我们不接受
First,
第一
I haven't accepted Hengjiu's offer for now.
我暂时没有接受恒久的邀请
Mind you, for now.
注意是暂时
Second,
第二
you're not the reason I stay.
你们不是我留下来的理由
Face reality.
要认清现实
Third,
第三
my training
我的训练
requires full commitment.
那就是要全身心投入
If you can't do it,
如果做不到
there's no need to continue.
那就没有必要进行
Why don't we
要不然
stop training for today?
今天就先别训练了
Everyone take a break.
大家都休息一下
First,
第一
I haven't accepted Hengjiu's offer for now.
我暂时没有接受恒久的邀请
Mind you, for now.
注意是暂时
Second,
第二
you're not the reason I stay.
你们不是我留下来的理由
Face reality.
要认清现实
He probably
他大概
really will leave.
真的会走吧
What will happen to the kids if he leaves?
他走了孩子们怎么办
Ms. Lin.
小林老师
Our teacher asked us to borrow 4 tires,
我们老师叫我们借四个轮胎
but there are only 3 here.
可是这边只有三个哎
Reserve them earlier next time.
下次早点约
Alright. Let's go.
那好吧 走
Ms. Lin, I'm here to return the equipment.
老师来还器材
Hello, Ms. Lin.
林老师好
Ms. Lin,
小林老师
don't be too sad.
你也别太难过啊
Compared to us,
和我们比起来
Yongchuan Hengjiu is indeed much better.
永川恒久确实好太多了
It's understandable that Coach wants to leave.
教练要走能理解
Coach hasn't said he's leaving yet.
教练目前还没说要走呢
Only a fool wouldn't know how to choose.
傻子才不知道怎么选择呢
It's normal to give up on us.
放弃我们很正常
Don't say that.
别这么说
Even if Coach goes to Yongchuan Hengjiu,
就算教练去了永川恒久
it's not your fault.
也不是你们的问题
You all play very well.
你们都踢得很好
Everyone wants to move up in life.
人往高处走嘛
We understand this.
这个道理我们都明白
Thank you, Ms. Lin.
谢谢你小林老师
You don't need to comfort us anymore.
不用再安慰我们了
Anyway,
反正
we've always been the abandoned ones.
我们一直都是被抛弃的人
We're used to it.
我们都习惯了
Ms. Lin,
小林老师
are we still training tomorrow?
那明天我们还训练吗
Never mind.
算了
Pretend I didn't ask.
当我没问